- So you look a little blurry , man . - This is my home .
Let me zoom out on you .
- Okay . - Okay .
Good morning .
- Got it ? - Okay , I got you .
- This is my home . - Okay .
Which I am leaving the comforts of for the weekend
to explore the Blair Witch .
Some essential reading , How to Stay Alive in the Woods ,
' cause you never know what 's going to happen .
And this is a very important book
because it has the article about what happened at Coffin Rock .
- That looks pretty old . - Yeah ,
it 's totally old . And this is my field notebook .
- Hey , it 's Mr. Punctuality . - Hey .
How the hell are you this morning ?
Tired .
So I got the CP up .
Good . That 's important
' cause that 's what we 're shooting on .
No one knows I took it , but I got it .
All right , come on , into the house . Come on , come on .
I can see you .
I 'm going to bump into shit . I 'm walking backwards now .
Okay , we don 't want to fuck up the cameras before we leave .
Hey , nice camera , man .
Alright , I know I 'm hitting the steps .
So , where 's Mikey at ?
We have to go get him .
Okay .
We 're supposed to get him at 8 : 30 .
Which means we 're already going to be behind schedule ,
- but it 's important to have juice . - That 's cool .
Relax .
You got the hotel and shit ? Everything set ?
Yeah , we 're staying at the Lone Star .
Can you turn the fucking camera off me , please ?
Okay .
Thank you .
I guess you 're Mike .
Here , wait ... Stop , stop .
Don 't we get to meet your mama ?
See you later , Mum !
How are you , Mike ? It 's nice to meet you .
I 'm tired , but I 'm doing good . I 'm real excited about this .
- Thank you for the opportunity . - I 'm very glad .
Well , thank you for getting the equipment together .
We 're totally grateful .
We got rice , we got Mott 's Fruit Punch .
Oatmeal raisin , baby .
- Ultimate camp food . - Marshmallows ...
Feel how soft . Soft ...
- Hey ! - You weasel .
Marshmallows ...
Ooh ...
Do you believe in ghosts ?
Have you ever heard of the Blair Witch ?
It 's ... It actually sounds kind of familiar .
My older sister went to Blair High School .
I want ... I want to get a little bit in here .
Give me a sec , man . I 'm going to set this camera up over here .
We 're relatively tightly scheduled .
I tried to give us some room .
We 're not interviewing Mary until 5 ,
but I cannot stress enough the importance of being on time .
So what 's first ?
- First is the cemetery ? - First is the cemetery .
You guys want to get the ceremonial first slate ?
Absolutely .
Here he is , filling out our first slate for our first shot .
Should we all , like , cut our fingers open and bleed on it ?
A little bloodletting on the slate ?
No , we 'll save that for later .
Kiss it . Kiss the slate .
It 's the first slate .
First slate . Marked by my lipstick .
Mikey , first slate . Kiss it . Good luck .
He licked it . God bless him .
You 're not supposed to eat it . We need that for the rest of the shoot .
This is Burkittsville , formerly Blair .
It is a small , quiet Maryland town ,
much like a small , quiet town anywhere .
No more than 20 families laid their roots here
over 200 years ago , many of whom remain either on this hill or in the town below .
There are an unusually high number of children laid to rest here ,
most of whom passed in the 1940s .
Yet , no one in the town seems to recall anything unusual about this time .
To us , anyway .
Yet , legend tells a different story . One whose evidence is all around us ,
etched in stone .
Well , we have shot the first scene . The cemetery scene .
The opening is shot .
- This is , uh ... - This is our salad .
- It 's our souvenir - HEATHER : Yeah , this is our souvenir ,
from our very first ... our very first shot ...
of our very first day , of our very first scene on 16mm
and we are proud of this salad .
- We 're doing a documentary . - Yeah ?
About the Blair Witch .
- Have you heard of the Blair Witch ? - Oh , yeah .
That 's an old , old , old story .
As I remember , Mr. Parr was an old hermit .
- Right . - And he lived up on a mountain .
He had a place up there .
Been there for a long , long time .
- You 've heard of the Blair Witch ? - Several times .
Several times ? And what was the first incident ?
I 've heard stories about her from people and neighbours and stuff like that .
But also I saw a documentary on the Discovery Channel , or somewhere ,
- once about her . - Really ?
About the ghosts and legends of Maryland .
Sort of in the winter , I guess ,
the fall or the winter of 1940 , some of the young kids started to disappear .
Nobody knew anything about why they were ...
Why they were disappearing .
The creepiest ...
The creepiest story about her ...
That 's kind of an omen , isn 't it ?
... that I ever heard was that two men were out hunting ,
and they were camped near the cabin , or something ,
that she 's supposed to haunt .
No , no !
And they disappeared off the face of the Earth .
- No . - Really ?
Okay , it 's all right , Ingrid . I 'm just telling a scary story ,
- but it 's not true . - It 's not true .
Finally , one day , old Mr. Parr come down into the market
and said , " I 'm finally finished . "
And what did he mean by that ?
Well , I guess nobody knew at first ,
but the police finally went up on the mountain
and they searched his house
and they found the bodies of seven kids from the area .
- Wow . - Those were the seven kids that were missing .
Then they brought them out of the woods , one at a time .
It was just a terrible thing ,
just tore the whole community up .
The wives apparently went looking for them ,
and the found their camp site . The fire was still burning .
Right .
The deer they had hunted was in the process of being gutted ,
it looked like someone was still working there and camping there ...
Right .
But the men were nowhere to be found .
Their clothes were there , everything was there .
- And they never-ever found them ? - They never found the men .
All my life , really , I 've believed in witches and ghosts and all that stuff .
Do you believe that there are some in this area ?
Oh , definitely .
- Do you believe in witchcraft ? - No .
- No ? - No , sir .
Are you a religious man ?
- Yep . - All righty .
Pretty creepy stuff .
I believe there 's something happening with her .
And you think that it 's possible that she 's still up there now ?
- I don 't go up there . - You don 't go up there ?
Yeah , I believe enough not to go up there .
And they say that the woods are all haunted up there
and stuff like that , but ...
What do they say ? How are they haunted ?
I don 't ... There really isn 't many people that say that it 's haunted ,
but there was this old woman , Mary Brown , who used to ...
- Mary Brown ? - Yeah , and she was kind of a crazy lady .
How was she seen by the community ?
Crazy .
That 's it . The American flag . That 's Mary 's house .
I 'm going to grab her and bring her out .
Why don 't you take a look around
and see where the best light is , all right ?
Okay .
This is Mary 's gate .
I 'm not even sure how I pull this open .
Okay ... that 's a little odd .
Oh , shit . I 've made her gate fall apart .
Shit .
' Cause something interesting
happened to you , actually , at one point in your life .
You had an encounter with the Blair Witch ?
Yes . That is a really , kind of , scary story .
To , kind of , make ends meet ,
my dad and I would go fishing down by Tappy 's Creek .
- Right . - And , you know , it 's in Burkittsville .
I was lying down on the leaves , a pile of leaves ,
kind of watching my pole and looking up at the sky .
- Sure . - And all of a sudden ,
- I felt like something was near me . - Right .
You know , kind of an eerie feeling .
It was like a woman ,
only on her arms and on her hands and everything it was like hair .
Like a real dark , almost black , hair .
- Like a horse . - Like fur ?
Yeah , like a fur . Like horse fur .
- Then on her arms , she had a shawl ... - Right .
Wool shawl over her .
And she scared you ?
- She threatened you ? - And she didn 't say anything ,
but she just kept staring , and then she opened up her shawl ...
And what was under there ?
And under there was hair on her body like a horse .
So she was hairy from head to toe ?
Yeah , and her legs ...
- And you could see she was a female . - Right . How about her face ?
It was just kind of , like , strange-looking .
Thank God , she 's not in the film business .
I mean , can you imagine working with her ?
She thinks she is in the film business . She also says she 's a ballerina .
- Get out . - She says she 's a historian
writing a book on American history ...
- I heard that . - ... and that she 's a scientist
who does research at the Department of Energy .
I fucked up on Mary .
I 'm checking my depth of field chart to see how bad .
So you measured for metres ? What ? We 're not in Europe .
Yeah , the fucking lens has metres on it , okay .
It also has our system .
No , it had metres on it . Look .
This is an American camera , though .
All those are metres .
What about the brown ones ?
The brown ones are feet .
Yeah , the brown ones are on there , right ?
Yeah , but the white ones are obvious .
But I thought you 've used this camera before , man .
I 've used it , like , once before .
How do we feel about today , guys ?
- I learned a lot , man . - Yeah .
You learned a lot about Mary Brown ?
No , I learned a lot about , like , fucking ...
Sixteen ?
Just shooting out here . Just shooting doc .
- Are you alright ? - Are you gonna die ?
I ain 't gonna die , pa .
The witch will heal you out there .
- Kicked some ass today . - Cheers , cheers .
- Very good day . - Excellent day .
Very good first day .
Okay , we 're going to do an equipment check ,
but I 'm going to call my mum .
Okay , I 've got a bag of Utz and a beer .
And we don 't really need to get that on film .
So , I guess you 're covered , then .
Could you just run it for a couple of feet for me
so we can check that it 's okay ?
Sure .
I just want to hear if this mag is loaded properly ,
so we can shoot some stuff .
Okay , that 's good . That 's good .
- That 's good , thank you . - Okay .
Let 's be relaxed ' cause we 've got a really , really long day tomorrow .
Today was cake compared to tomorrow . We 're going to do a lot of hiking .
We 're going to have a lot of weight on our backs .
I 'm preparing .
That 's what we 're preparing for .
Shut up , you smartass . Pour me a shot , please .
- I 'm freaking out . - You can 't do that .
- You 're the director . - Yes , I ... You know , at this point ,
I fucking have to do that , all right ?
I fucking have to . Do we have any weed ?
Here I go .
Drink , drink .
I fucking hate Scotch .
- There 's my friend Josh . - Hey .
- How are you ? - I 'm hurting .
I 'm not ready for that thing that you 're doing , like , you know ...
I know you don 't like it . Okay .
Hello .
Welcome to Day Two .
The trail is somewhere along here . We shouldn 't miss it .
It should be pretty , pretty obvious .
You guys say you know something about the Blair Witch ?
I 've heard the myths . I don 't really believe much in it .
" The myth " ?
That 's all I think it is .
Damn fool kids 'll never learn .
What 'd you say , sir ?
I said , " You damn fool kids 'll never learn . "
Shut up .
- " Damn fool kids 'll never learn " ? - That 's what I said .
And what makes you say that ?
First of all , can I have your permission
to put your image on video for the purposes
of a documentary entitled The Blair Witch Project ?
I don 't care much about that , but ...
Well , you have to say yes or no , sir .
- Watch it . - Sorry .
Yeah , sure , that 's all right .
Yeah , some girl back in the late 1800s ,
- Robin Weaver I believe her name was ... - Right .
... supposedly just wandered off , disappeared into the woods .
Wasn 't no " supposedly " about it . They wandered off .
- Okay , so she wandered off . - And she got lost .
She got lost .
- Three days later ... - There wasn 't no " supposedly . "
Three days later , she just appears back on her grandmother 's porch .
Right .
- And everybody 's mystified about it . - Right .
- She was babbling something ... - She had a tale to tell , too , though .
Yeah , she was babbling something about the ...
An old woman whose feet never touched the ground .
I 'll tell you , I saw ,
right up there by that tree ,
- up the creek ... I told you that . - Right , I know .
About a hundred yards , I saw a white misty thing
that I can 't tell what it is , one day .
It was , like , a grey ... Like , grey vapour rising out of the trees ?
Right out of the water .
Right out of the water , near the trees .
Up the side of the tree ,
and it disappeared over them ...
Now you 're full of it .
I mean , anybody worth their salt around here
knows that this area 's been haunted by that old woman for years .
That 's bullshit .
This view is ever so amazing .
Flat ass .
How 's the speed , a little more ?
Yeah , you can do it .
Could you slide up so we get more of your ass crack ?
This is some serious woods we 're heading into .
Excited ?
You got it .
I hope he 's not rolling off a whole shitload of stock .
How many feet are you shooting ?
Uh ... about twenty so far .
Oh , okay . Good .
Yeah .
I could help you , but I 'd rather stand and record .
Okay .
Packs are on ?
- We 're rocking . Let 's rock . - We 're ready to go .
- We got to go up to the shack , the shanty ? - Yeah .
Wow .
Yeah , it 's like we 're off to the Andes or something .
Oh , my God , this is a very heavy backpack .
On our way to Coffin Rock . We are totally on track .
I know exactly where we are now .
We 're a bit behind schedule ,
I 'm very concerned about losing light today .
So we 're crossing this , yeah ? Okay .
- Mikey , throw me the video camera . - No , don 't .
I wanna get her going across , man .
I see a dirty behind .
There it is . See ?
That 's Coffin Rock .
Go .
" They went into the woods prepared to find death .
" What they found was a desecration of humanity
" at the site which trappers have often referred to as Coffin Rock .
" On top of the rock formation
" the story of the torture inflicted upon these brave five men unfolded .
" Each was bound to the other ,
" each man 's hands bound to the next man 's feet ,
" forming a solid structure out of the men .
" Blood at the edges of the head indicate that this act had committed ...
" Been committed while each was alive and able-bodied enough to struggle .
" In the torso of each man the intestines had been torn out crudely .
" On each man 's sun-bleached face was inscribed indecipherable writing ,
" cut into their flesh with an eerie precision .
" The men , still entranced by the horror of what had happened ,
" left the scene to find the sheriff ,
" and did not sketch the writing
" and did not remove the bodies from the rock .
" Upon return , vultures were seen at the rock ,
" but upon inspection ,
" the bodies had been removed by persons unknown .
" The search party claimed that the stench of death was still thick
" and whomever had taken the bodies had done so in a matter of hours . "
That happened here at Coffin Rock .
It felt really rushed ' cause I really want to get to camp ,
and it 's 4 : 52 and we 're going to be late .
We 're going to be losing light soon .
But , I mean , I can always use the shot without me in it
because I recorded sound in the rock reading the whole thing .
So , I 'm sure I can edit it together somehow .
It 's starting to rain .
- What did you do , rent this thing ? - Yeah .
I don 't have a tent for three people .
- You know , I 'm not used to ... - No , I 'm just wondering .
I 'm not usually travelling with two men , if you know what I 'm saying .
It is pouring rain right now . We can 't even get a fire going .
Show the kids at home what the stick is for .
Look at that .
We 've got our very own leaning post .
If you get too much ass smell in the night ...
Okay , who wouldn 't let me have a cigarette in the tent ,
but he 's allowed to fart as much as he wants ?
- I really don 't think it 's ... - No , I never gave Mike any fart allowance .
So , you heard noises last night ?
- I totally heard noise . - See , the problem is ,
I sleep like a fucking rock .
It was like there were two separate noises
coming from two layers of space over here
and one of them was kind of , like ...
One of them could have possibly been an owl ,
but the other one was , like , a cackling ...
- Was a definite ... - No way .
It was a total cackling , man .
If I heard a cackling , I would 've shit in my pants .
- Where 'd we start out yesterday ? - Off the map .
Off the map .
' Cause I knew where we were going .
Though I know there was some confusion ,
- but today ... - Wait , wait , wait . Say that again .
I said , " I knew where we were going . "
Wait , wait , wait , wait , wait .
- Would that be a full-of-shit statement ? - No , I did ...
- Would that be a full-of-shit statement ? - I did know where ...
All I 'm saying is that you got us lost , man .
- For a very brief amount of time . - Okay .
- Just don 't get us lost today . - It was very brief .
Yeah , serious .
I 'm not . I know where all of these places are .
They 're all very well-documented .
So , what 's up ? Are you happy
with the way the documentary 's going ?
- Yes , I am . Yeah . - Yeah ?
And I 'm very pleasantly surprised by our little Mikey .
- " Our little Mikey " ? - Our little Mikey .
- So , what 's up ? - He 's a very spirited young man .
I mean , what 's your take on the Blair Witch at this point ?
- Do you think she exists ? - I don 't know . I don 't know .
Heather , I really wish you 'd found a trail ...
There 's a trail on top of this hill , don 't worry .
- It is a trail . - This is not a trail .
We like shortcuts , don 't we ?
We like level shortcuts .
We don 't like mountainous shortcuts .
It 's a little warmer today ,
so this is the first time we 're seeing Mike 's chest .
It 's really hard to pick up on video , actually .
Mike has really sporadic hair patterns on his chest .
It 's like a symbol , man .
It 's , like , blank , hairy , blank , hairy .
You should see my ass .
Look , look . It 's fucking Uruguay , right there , right there .
- Wow . - There 's Paraguay over here .
- Yeah , whatever . - Look , I think I see Bolivia .
What killed this dead mouse ?
Witchcraft ?
How about God ?
Is that the Blair Witch ?
No . I think it 's Heather taking a piss .
You know , this is really not too good . I really have to go .
- Don 't torture me . - Go .
We are hot on the cemetery trail .
- It should only be a ... - Says you .
- What ? - Says you .
Says me , of course . And ...
We should be hitting it in about 90 minutes .
- You guys cool with that ? - What ?
- 90 minutes . - As long as you know where we 're going .
Can you hang ? I know exactly where we 're going .
Josh feels it 's necessary to look
at the map now , even though I know
where we 're going and we 're going straight ahead up there .
If you 've known where we 're going , we wouldn 't be hiking like ...
We 're in the middle of the fucking woods , man .
- How could you possibly know ? - Some of it is off-trail hiking .
Because people told you ?
" Oh , yeah , there 's a cemetery back in there . "
If we 're lost , admit that first , because ...
We 're not ... I know we 're not lost .
You knew that yesterday , too , and you knew that twice today .
Look ... No , bullshit , and I ...
We have not been lost at all today .
That 's ...
- That is not true . - Not once . I know where we 're going .
Okay , this is where we were .
Let me tell you what you said to us .
" It 's , like , two miles away . " Then , it 's like , " Two hours away ... "
- Okay , just , just chill . Just chill . - " Three hours away . "
Maybe it 's four hours away . How could you ...
- Did you agree to do this project ? - I did . I agreed to a scouted-out project .
I didn 't agree to just trounce around the woods .
It is scouted out , and I told you getting to the location
- wasn 't going to be easy . - Mike , Mike ... Okay ! Guys !
- I 've got $ 1,500 worth of equipment on me . - Guys , it 's cool , it 's cool .
Please , you 're being a smartass , you 're being a smartass ...
Let 's just ... We 're looking at the map .
- We 're going to find this the best we can . - Okay .
I can totally find this .
This is where we were .
We 're going more or less this way .
Mika , what 's your call ? I mean , where do you think we 're going ?
I 'll tell you the truth .
This is , like ... This is Greek to me .
- Right . - It 's useless .
Exactly .
So , I 'm just putting my trust in you
that you know where it is .
Well , good .
Although I got to tell you , I don 't fully trust you .
And I ... No , I 'm not going to say it .
What ?
Nothing . I don 't know why you have to have every conversation on video , man .
- Tape some ambiance . - ' Cause we 're making a documentary .
Not about us getting lost .
We 're making a documentary about a witch .
I have a camera . Doesn 't hurt because
we 'll all look back on this and laugh heartily , believe me .
Baby steps , man , baby steps .
Just breathe and don 't look down , maybe ?
- No , you 've got to look down . - You 're gonna have to crawl .
- I 'm hitting the crawl . - Cool .
Think about how cool the fucking cemetery
is gonna be when we get there .
Think of the joy of being in a really good film .
- Okay , shut the fuck up . - Okay , I 'm quiet .
Shit . How am I gonna do this ?
- Okay , Mikey ? - Yeah ?
Dude , there 's no way you 're coming across
with your DAT on your belly , man .
- No way , man . - There 's no chance .
How are we going to get the DAT across then ?
It 's really fucking hard , man .
- How are we gonna get the DAT across ? - The one this morning
with the moss was cool .
This is slippery as shit .
How are we gonna get the DAT across ?
I don 't know . Let me get out of here and put my pack down .
I 'll just go back and forth .
You want to go back and forth ? You could do it that way .
I didn 't want to do this at all , but ...
Okay , let 's do ...
Yeah , we 'll do it back and forth .
Oh , Christ ...
What 'd you drop ?
I didn 't drop anything .
- The tree just broke on me . - The log broke .
Oh , fuck .
We 're very , very , very close now .
You guys excited ?
Okay .
What 's this ?
Wow !
What is this ?
Dude . Guys ?
Do you remember something that Mary Brown said the other day ?
What was the story from the Bible that she was telling us ?
Fuck , I wasn 't listening to her ' cause I thought she was a lunatic .
It was Esau , but it was something about a pile of rocks .
She was totally telling us about her rocks , man .
What the fuck was it about a pile of rocks ?
Does anybody remember ?
- " To live your life ... - This is like ...
" Live your life ... "
Looks like an Indian burial ground , man .
See , I don 't know if this counts . Three ... Four ...
Five ... Six ...
Seven .
Witches in days gone by were roasted just like my Vienna sausage .
Flames are licking you like the devil there , Josh .
Just sit right back and you 'll hear a tale A tale of a fateful trip
That started on this desert isle Aboard this tiny ship
Yeah , but this ship has a good captain , not a fat , beer-guzzling guy in a blue shirt .
He wasn 't beer-guzzling .
They had no beer on the island , man .
If they 'd had beer , they would have had , like , big-ass orgies .
You 're kind of like the Captain and Mike 's kind of like your Gilligan .
- No offense . - That 's all right .
I mean that as a compliment . Gilligan was a funny guy .
The Captain was fat , though .
Well . Okay , let 's call it a thin captain ...
Let 's not call it " the Captain " anymore , you illiterate TV people .
It 's the Skipper .
- No more " captain . " - Oh , my .
Here we are back at the rock again . The rock thing .
The cemetery deal .
I just want to be careful not to get in the film shot .
It certainly is odd .
You didn 't just knock that over .
Please , tell me you didn 't just knock that over .
I just knocked it over .
That 's not very nice .
Let me put it back .
Can 't be too careful .
What did you think ?
It was , you know , the same thing , only darker .
Yeah , pretty much . All right .
Bag it up , put it away .
Hello ?
Shit . The light .
- We were sleeping . - Do you want this ?
Just keep it by the opening in the tent .
Shhh !
Listen .
Hello ?
It 's all around us .
That is fucking weird .
Michael , are you saying you 're not coming down ?
- I ain 't going down there . - Why not ?
Because I 'm not . I don 't hear shit ...
Because you 're fucking scared .
- Because I don 't hear anything anymore . - Because you 're fucking scared .
We heard ... You could not deny hearing it .
Get your ass out . What 's the big deal ?
- This rain fucking blows , man . - I know .
It 's raining very heavily .
Thank my mum for giving me rain gear for my 18th birthday .
God bless her .
What do you think that was last night ?
- Personally ? - Yeah .
I think it was someone fucking with your head .
But nobody knows we 're out here .
Yeah , but you ever see Deliverance ?
Did you understand at all where I was coming from ?
That I just wanted ... Whatever it was , I didn 't know ...
- You were freaking out . You bugged me out . - I was freaking out .
I woke up all of a sudden and shit 's going down .
All I can think is , " I got to get it . I got to get it . "
All I want it on ... I want it on sound , I want it on 16 .
If anything , if we can see anything , I want to see it on 16 .
Well , it sounded to me like a bunch of people running around ,
and I 'm not down with messing with the locals or whatever .
I don 't know who the hell would come out here .
What bugs me out is that we 're so damn deep in the woods
and people are going to try and ...
And come out here and mess with us ,
then they got to have something wrong with them .
And I 'm not going to play with that .
How do we know it was people ?
Well , even if it wasn 't , I 'm not going to play with that , either .
Fuck , man .
This has been a very long day .
A very wet , very long day .
Nobody 's really speaking to me at the moment .
Dude , I don 't remember a portion of this from walking in .
What ?
I don 't remember a portion of this from walking in from the car .
Well , we have to go a little differently
to get back , because we went around in a curve a little bit .
I 'm telling you guys , two more hours max .
If the way we came in was the fastest ,
why the fuck are we going back a different way ?
Because we have to go around . We came ...
That was the most direct way to hit our two locations .
Now , this is the most direct way back to the car .
- Seriously , really ? - Yes . Seriously .
- You know exactly what 's going on ? - Yes .
Let 's just keep going .
Yeah , we 'll wait five minutes and do a map check .
All right .
Okay , we just did a map check
and it seems like we 're still pretty much on trail .
That 's not what I said .
No , I think we 're all right . Come on , let 's just keep going .
We took a map reading . We just follow what the compass says .
We 're going straight ahead . We 're going that way . That way .
We are in the middle of nowhere .
We 've been in the middle of nowhere for two days .
The car is parked in the middle of nowhere almost .
Like , look at this shit , man . This is nothing .
Okay , let 's just keep going , all right ?
- I think we should camp . - Get the fuck out of here .
Why ? Because you don 't know where we 're going ?
No , because I think we 're still a ways off from the car
and it 's going to be getting dark real soon .
- Look , I 'm not saying for certain ... - We 're not camping here .
- Get us home . Turn the camera off . - Maybe we 're near the car .
- Get us home . - Give me the fucking map .
Give me the map . Heather , give me the map .
- Turn the camera off and give me the map . - Turn the camera off and get us home .
I 'm not turning the camera off . I want to mark this occasion .
- Give me the map . - The map is in my pocket .
You 're going to have to wait a second .
- You want to see the map ? - Goddamn !
If we keep our heads together , we 'll be just fine .
- Fucking bullshit ! - Mike , chill .
Just relax , Mike .
Don 't fucking tell me to relax !
Let 's walk up , find a tree
to sit under or some shit , check the map ...
Yes , can we find a place to sit to check the map , please ?
- Are you happy ? - I 'm not happy , no .
But the car is not far .
We 're just not going to be able to find it in the dark .
Are you absolutely , positively sure ?
Yes . I 'm so sorry , man .
We can probably still get the DAT back tomorrow .
We have to . We have to .
We will . We will .
We will get the DAT back before it 's due back tomorrow .
I 've got to get the fucking camera back . I got to fucking work .
- Everything will get back tomorrow . - I got to work .
I 'm supposed to be at work tomorrow at 9 : 00 , man .
- I know . - It 's fine .
Let 's just go to sleep . Let 's go to sleep .
Let 's camp . Let 's just fucking camp , okay ?
I want to get it . I want to get it from inside the tent .
Whatever it was last night , it sounds like the same fucking thing .
Where 's my boots ? Oh , fuck , it 's cold .
Hello ?
Oh , shit . It 's fucking freezing .
There .
What ?
I hear it .
I don 't hear shit .
You hear that ?
Shit .
Hello ?
Oh , fuck .
I think it 's just a deer .
It could be deer , I guess .
I don 't fucking think it 's deer , though , man . It sounds exactly like the shit last night .
It 's on all sides of us .
- It 's got to be just , like , a deer . - It was a deer , man .
- I think it was a fucking ... - It wasn 't like last night .
- Did you hear anything ? - Yes ! Fucking listen .
Okay , let 's get it on DAT . Let 's get it on DAT . Be quiet .
- Okay , it 's on . - Okay .
Jesus Christ ! What the fuck is that ? Fuck !
It 's obviously not scared by our yelling .
- But it sounds like footsteps . - I know . That 's a fucking person .
Mikey , I 'm not seeing shit on video .
I 'm going to leave the rest for DAT , all right ?
I 'm going to stay out here with you , though .
You got to fucking stay out here with me .
- I am , I am . - What time is it ?
Is it fucking anywhere near morning right now ?
- Let 's see ... - Please say it 's fucking 5 : 00 or some shit .
- 3 : 00 . - Fuck ! This is bullshit .
This is absolutely fucking crazy .
I 'm sorry , Mike . We should be out of here already .
This has got nothing , nothing to do with what the fuck we 're here for .
I swear to God , this is bullshit .
Woke up this morning just , like , two seconds ago ,
and there are piles of rocks outside of our tent .
There are three , actually .
Are you seriously fucking positive those weren 't there
when we went to bed last night ?
I am seriously fucking positive
these were not here .
How would we have , like , just made a campsite
in between three piles of rocks , just by coincidence ?
You don 't think this is strange ?
This is way fucking weird ,
but it really doesn 't matter at this point
because all I want to do is get to the goddamn car .
Whatever it is , man ... Whatever it is at this point ... Whatever it is ...
I know , I know . We have to get back to the car .
- We 're obviously not wanted here ... - Okay , okay ...
- ... so let 's get the hell out . - We 're going home .
We have to go ... We have to get the DAT back anyway .
- I realise that . That 's what I 'm saying . - Okay , let 's go .
Let 's get the DAT back . Let 's get our shit packed up .
- We 're out of here . We 're out of here . - Let 's walk .
- Can we just walk ? - Yes . We 're out of here .
Okay . Cool .
I can 't believe we have to leave just when shit 's happening .
Heather , put the fucking camera down . Let 's pack up the tent .
- Okay . Hang on . - Let 's get the fuck out of the woods , okay ?
- Come on . - No , I 'm not fucking scared .
I 'm just tired , I 'm hungry , I 'm fucking , like ...
I 'm just fucking done , man .
- All right . - I 'm just fucking done .
Did you take it ?
No , I didn 't take the fucking map , man .
I 'm not playing head games .
If anyone 's playing head games , you 're playing head games .
But I 'm not playing head games .
I don 't have it . We have to go .
I 'm serious . I don 't have it .
- Are you fucking serious ? - I 'm fucking serious .
I don 't have the map , okay ?
- Heather , that is so not cool , man . - I know it 's not cool .
- That is so not cool . - I know it 's not cool .
That is ... That ...
I mean , that 's the fucking , like , least responsible thing
you could have possibly done , man .
I know that .
You really don 't have it ?
- One of you have got to have the map . - No , I don 't have the map .
We gave it back to you after map check yesterday .
You 've always had the map .
I know , and I 've always had the map in the same place ,
and if it 's not there , one of you had to have taken it .
I 'm not going into your fucking pants to get your goddamn map , man .
I just checked my pocket , it 's not in my pants .
Look , would I go in and get your map ?
All I want to do is get out of here , man . I 'm not fucking around .
- That 's all I want , too , man . - Let 's go .
No , you want to stay here , you want to film rocks ,
you want to look around , you want to fucking , like ,
- get this , you want to get that . - Let 's go .
- Which way are we walking ? - That way .
Dude , we 're in the middle of the fucking woods !
We 're in the middle of the goddamn woods . We can walk anyway ...
We 're going this way
' cause that 's the way we 've been going for a fucking day .
We 're going this way , and that 's it . We gotta come across something .
I gave you the map , Josh .
- I gave you back the map , Heather . - I gave you the map .
I gave you back the map .
- Let 's just go . - All I 'm saying is , we can move
as fast as we want , but if we have no fucking clue where we 're moving to ,
then it really doesn 't matter , does it ?
We 're following the creek and Mike seems satisfied with that .
Would you guys stop it ?
We are gone . We are fucked , we are done , we are dead , we 're fucked .
I 'm just going to stay here .
When you guys find somebody , tell them I 'm under this tree with the vine .
All blame aside ...
- This is really fucked up . - I know .
- Yeah . - I know .
We really , really , really need to work together .
- Exactly . Exactly . - I realise this .
Okay , so we deal with the fact that my camera 's not going to be back ,
your DAT 's not going to be back .
No blame from now on about that shit .
Look , serious , the area 's not that fucking big .
Exactly .
It 's very hard to get lost in America these days ,
and it 's even harder to stay lost .
So , we have that on our side . What ?
We 're doing a pretty goddamn good job of being lost .
Because at this point , when you 're not home today ,
when I 'm not home today , people are going to start noticing .
Like , my girlfriend is definitely going to notice
that I 'm not back today , and that I haven 't fucking called .
I mean , if I called , it would be one thing .
But , you know , if I just get back , like , don 't get back , period ,
and I don 't call , she 's going to notice .
Which means that by tonight , if we haven 't found shit ,
someone 's going to be looking for us .
Oh , no .
Don 't come this way . Go another way .
Go down there . I just got my whole shit wet .
Oh , shit . Well , let 's try it this way .
I don 't think you want to try this way . I think you want to try the other way .
If we didn 't have these fucking packs , it would be so much easier .
- I don 't mean to laugh . - Dude , my feet are wet .
Are you ... Is that Michael laughing ?
- Shut the fuck up and cross the stream . - He 's laughing .
Michael , that is the first time I 've heard you laugh in days .
I 'm really happy you find it very amusing
that I 'm going to be incredibly uncomfortable
for the rest of the day .
Dude , uncomfortable just does not even ...
Can we keep going , please ?
No , we 're going to chill out .
I thought you wanted to get to the car .
Oh , boy !
- Okay , come on . Let 's get up here . - Oh , shit .
You guys weren 't lying to me about the map , were you ?
' Cause this just seems like you guys are having
just a little bit too much fun for my taste .
- Heather . - No , we 're just going a little stir-crazy .
Heather , Heather , if you make me yell at this point ,
I 'm going to have to yell at you , man .
Come on , seriously , if you have the map , I just want to know that you have it .
That would just make me happy , just to know that you have it .
Heather ...
If I know that you have it , and I can at least see it ,
I will feel much better .
Like , all we 're trying to do is be cool with you .
I find it very cool that I get laughed at
because my shoes are wet for the rest of the day .
I find it fucking hilarious .
Heather , dude , all our shoes are wet . We were laughing at the situation .
- Fine . - We 're fucking hungry , we 're fucking tired .
What the hell else are we supposed
- to do at this point ? - You know what ?
I kicked the ... I 'm sorry , it 's fucked up , it 's fucked up .
But I kicked that fucking map into the creek yesterday .
It was useless .
I kicked that fucker into the creek .
I fucking hope he 's kidding .
- Mike ? - Holy shit .
I really fucking hope he 's kidding .
Mike , are you kidding ?
- I really fucking hope he 's kidding . - Mike , are you fucking kidding ?
I 'm sorry , man . I 'm sorry .
You 've got to be kidding me .
- You have got to fucking be kidding me ! - You think this is a fucking game ?
- Get the fuck off me , man . - What the fuck ?
Are you out of your fucking mind ?
No , I 'm not out of my mind ! That map wasn 't doing shit for us .
Do you realise ... Not to you ,
- but I knew what the fuck that map said ! - I 'm sorry !
- You are a fucking asshole ! - I 'm sorry .
- You 're a fucking asshole ! And if we ... - That map wasn 't doing shit all day !
If we get hurt or we die out here , it 's your fucking fault !
It is your fucking fault ! Do you understand ?
I can 't believe you could be such an asshole !
- What the fuck were you thinking ? - You 're just fucking with my shit here !
Okay , no ... I 'm not , I 'm not ...
- That map was useless ! - If this was your own ...
- That map was useless ! - It was useless to you !
- It was useless to you ! - Bullshit !
Okay ... Okay .
This is not why I brought you out here , man .
- Okay . Okay . - I 'm sorry about the map , man .
- What can I say ? - " Sorry " ?
The map wasn 't doing shit .
Please , just don 't say " sorry . "
The map was not worth shit to you . I knew exactly
- where we were on that map . - It wasn 't worth shit to both of you .
- I asked you ... - I knew exactly where we were
- on that map ! - Listen to me !
Yesterday , I asked you what fucking river we were on ...
You shut up or I 'm going to fucking stick your head ...
Turn this fucking camera off !
Give me the compass .
You 've betrayed us all beyond ... Way fucking beyond ...
- Bullshit , man . - Give me the compass .
You betrayed us when you couldn 't get us out of the woods last night .
Yeah , thanks .
- Can I hold the fucking compass now ? - No !
- Can I hold the fucking compass ? - No .
I bought the compass .
- If you wanted a compass ... - I don 't give a shit .
You should have bought your own fucking compass .
You fucked us up . He fucked us up .
I don 't know why you can 't admit ...
Let 's just keep walking south .
... that you 've been screwed from the moment we got out here , man .
Because I haven 't ! Because I haven 't .
Heather , give me the compass ...
I 've been planning this project for two years . We 're walking south . Now !
- Give me the compass . - You fucking asshole !
Don 't knock me down because I will fucking knock you out !
- Give me the compass ... - Well I am walking south !
Fuck you both . Fuck you both !
Fuck you , bitch .
Okay , I 'm a bitch . I 'm a bitch ?
Your friend throws the map in the creek and I 'm a bitch ?
- Okay ! O-fucking-kay . - Fuck you .
Why are we stopped again ? Why ?
Why are we stopped ?
- Does ... Does anybody have a ... - Just don 't . Just don 't .
Does anybody have a reason why we 're stopped ?
That 's all I 'm asking you .
What about the plan to keep going south ? We all seemed very happy with that plan .
Why is that not a thing anymore ?
Jesus Christ .
I can 't understand you ?
- What ? - There 's all sorts of stuff down here !
- What kind of stuff ? - Like , voodoo shit .
- What ? - Like , voodoo stuff .
- It 's hanging all over . Look around you . - No way .
- They 're all over the place . - Holy shit .
Come up here , quick ! I need to use the CP .
Yeah , there 's all sorts of shit up here , man .
This is fucking crazy shit .
- Please , I got to get this on 16 . - Take the fucking camera .
- What the fuck is this ? - I have no idea .
Look at this shit , man .
Jesus Christ , that 's fucking creepy .
This is no redneck . No redneck is this creative .
- Can we get out of here now ? - Yeah , please ?
Okay , I 've got everything on video , man .
Jesus Christ , I didn 't even fucking see these , man .
Okay , I want to get as far away from here by dark as humanly possible .
That 's it , Heather .
Heather , you 've got enough , man . Let 's go .
- That 's enough ! - Stop taping ! Please , stop taping !
- We 've got it ! It 's enough ! - Okay .
Okay , okay , okay , we 're leaving right now .
Okay . Okay , we 're out of here . We 're out of here . I 'm leaving .
Come on ! Turn it off !
Help ! Help !
Please , help us !
Help us !
This is not the way to get out of here .
Fuck !
I think it 's safe to say at this point that we 're lost ,
and I don 't know what to do .
I think we should all get inside the tent .
All right .
Let 's not light a fire tonight .
- Yeah . - Because two nights in a row we 've lit a fire .
We didn 't light one the first night ...
- And nothing happened . - ... and nothing happened .
We light fires , they know . I haven 't heard anything follow us .
We should even turn that light off , too .
All right . All right .
Seriously , man . Anything that 's going to attract attention to us at this point .
Okay . Let 's just go to sleep .
What 's going on ?
Oh , God .
What 's that sound ?
Oh , Jesus !
- Jesus Christ , what if it 's ... - What was that ?
- Oh , Jesus Christ . - I 'm going to put jeans on .
Jesus ! Jesus !
Take the video camera . No , get the DAT ready .
I 'm going to take the video camera . I 'm gonna record this shit .
Oh , dear God ! Oh , dear God !
Go ! Fucking go !
Oh , God !
God ! Fucking God ! Fuck !
- Hurry up ! - I 'm coming !
My boots aren 't laced .
Oh , my God ! What the fuck is that ?
What the fuck is that ?
Shit !
Oh , my God !
Mike , where are you going ?
Holy shit .
Turn the lights off . Turn the lights off .
Turn that light off . Turn it off , Josh .
All lights off . All lights off .
- I 'm soaking . - It 's okay .
- What 's that ? - What the fuck is going on ?
What the fuck is going on ?
- Did you hear that baby screaming ? - Yes .
Shut the fuck up . There 's no fucking baby out there .
- Yes , there was . - There 's no fucking baby out there .
Okay . Okay . Okay .
I haven 't heard anything since we ran away .
Oh , my God , it 's cold .
- We should be quiet , okay ? - Okay , okay .
We should be quiet .
I don 't hear anything anymore . Maybe we should go back .
How long have we been here ?
I don 't know . A fucking hour .
The sun 's up . We 're okay now .
Let 's just get back . Let 's pack shit up .
- Let 's get out . - Okay .
What the fuck , man ?
- Where 's my pack ? - Your pack is right there . Where 's my pack ?
How come we 're getting fucked with like this ?
They just opened it up .
- They spilled all my fucking water . - That looks like slime , man .
It 's just water , man .
- Oh , it is slime . What the fuck is that ? - It 's slime , dude .
Let 's get this shit packed up and get out of here .
- Come on , Heather . Turn that thing off . - Heather , come on , let 's go .
Heather , let 's move it .
I 'm not interested in anything anymore . Let 's go .
- I know ! I know ! - So , turn it off .
Just relax for just a second . Have we gotten everything here ?
- Like I give a shit . - Whose shit was thrown around ?
- Who specifically ? - It 's my shit !
- My shit . - Why you ?
Let 's go ! Let 's go . Are you not scared enough ?
No , but why you ?
Yes , I am scared enough and I do want to go but it 's light now
- we have a couple of minutes . - No , we don 't have a couple of minutes !
- Let 's just see what happened here ! - We need to hike !
- Put the camera down . This is not funny . - I 'm coming .
Do I look like I 'm laughing at all ?
No , but you 're going around doing your documentary thing , man .
You 're still doing your fucking thing .
Don 't fucking ...
Then turn the goddamn thing off !
If you bite me one more time , I will throw you in the fucking woods .
You touch my camera one more time ,
- I 'll bite you again . - Turn that thing off !
- Sorry . - I didn 't mean it , okay ?
- Are you all right ? - I 'm fine . I just ...
I want to go home , but it 's important ... I just want to get what we can .
What the fuck ?
Is this possible ?
Okay , all right .
Here I go .
I hate crossing streams on logs .
If I never cross another stream on a log for the rest of my life ,
I will die a happy girl .
I see why you like this video camera so much .
- You do ? - It 's not quite reality .
Reality says we got to move .
No , but it 's totally like a filtered reality , man .
It 's like you can pretend everything 's not quite the way it is .
Just leave him alone for now .
- We need to go . - Just leave him alone for five minutes .
- Mike ... - Just leave him alone .
Five minutes . Come on . He 's lost it .
I know that , but we 're all on the brink
- of losing it . - I know we are .
- We got to take care of each other . - I know .
And there 's no way we 're taking care of him
if we 're going to throw the camera in his face if he 's crying .
- I know that . - I know you know .
I know we 're both about to lose it ,
- but let 's try and keep the last wits we have . - We have to ...
I understand we have to go . Believe me , I know .
It 's hard for all of us to hold it together . We need to get out of here
- in one piece , and this is not helping . - I know this .
You 're not telling me anything I don 't know .
- Just let him have his ... - Does anybody have a cigarette ?
- No , man . - No , there 's none left .
Nobody has any cigarettes ?
We 're out .
What the fuck was this blue jelly shit all over my shit ?
Let 's go . Let 's go .
If we keep going south , we will get out .
Please .
I don 't want to set up camp another fucking night , man .
- Josh , none of us do . - I know . I know you don 't .
Whatever it is , is going to come back . We know that for a fact .
We don 't know that for a fact .
It came three nights in a row , and it 's getting worse every night .
I would love to hear this right now . I really would .
I 'm just trying to say that , you know , we have to
- rationally say ... - I know .
They might very well go on forever compared to our footsteps .
Not possible .
- Not possible in this country . - Why is it not possible ?
Because this is America and it 's not possible .
We 've destroyed most of our natural resources .
Let 's just keep going .
How ... Okay .
I 'm not going to be a humourless pain in the ass .
But this I do not fucking understand .
No , that 's the tree we crossed . That tree is down . That 's the same one .
- Oh , God ! - No . Oh , no .
You 've got to be kidding me ! This is a joke !
- No ... - This is not funny !
Mike , just please stop .
Please ... Please stop .
Please stop .
- Please stop . - Oh , no !
No . No , Mike , it 's not the same log .
- It 's not the same log , Mike . - It 's the same one !
- Look , it 's not . - It is ! Open your eyes !
It 's not the same log .
It 's not ...
Fuck .
- Fuck ! - Oh , shit .
- Fuck ! - Fuck !
It 's the same log .
Fuck you , God !
Okay .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
Where do you want to go to camp ? I guess today south didn 't work out ,
so tomorrow we 'll go east . I don 't know what to say , Josh .
How the fuck did we walk south all day and wind up ...
We 've walked south all day , okay ? We walked south all fucking day .
I don 't know how we ended up here .
Do you expect me to do something or say something ?
What do you want to do , Josh ?
Josh ?
I want to make movies , Heather .
Isn 't that what we 're here to do ?
- Let 's make some movies . - Fuck you .
Fuck you . Really . Fuck you .
Please , let 's not fight . Please .
Come on , I can 't . I can 't listen to fighting . I can 't fight .
We 're screwed and that 's it . Please stop fighting .
Both of you .
I 'll do the first watch .
I got first watch .
Come on , you can do better than that .
This is not the place or the time , guys .
We have things to prepare for here .
Okay , here 's your motivation .
You 're lost , you 're angry in the woods , and no one here is here to help you .
There 's a fucking witch and she keeps leaving shit
- outside your door . - Josh .
There 's no one here to help you . She left little trinkets .
- Josh . - You fucking took one of them .
She ran after us . There 's no one here to help you .
- Josh ! - We walked for 15 hours today .
We ended up in the same place .
- There 's no one here to help you . - Just stop .
- Josh ! - That 's your motivation !
Would you please stop ?
That 's your motivation .
- Please stop . - Josh . Just quit it .
- She 's had enough . - Please stop .
Come on , man , you got her back . Good one .
No , she 's still making movies , man . That 's my point .
- Please stop . - This is my point here .
It 's all I fucking have left , okay ? Just please stop .
Please stop .
Just please stop yelling at me , please .
Come on , I 'm fucking tired of crying all day here .
We got to think like human beings . We have things to prepare for .
We got to make shifts . We got lots to do .
You going to write us a happy ending , Heather ?
Come on , man , turn it off .
You 're getting like she was . Come on , turn it off .
Dude , I can 't believe we 're even stitching those pants at this point , man .
Well , I 'm cold , man .
- I know . - I hear you .
I know .
The smallest comforts we can get are good .
Doesn 't it just seem absurd , though , at this point ?
Yes , it does .
A lot of things seem absurd .
Like sleeping right where we were pretty much sleeping last night .
That 's just fucking me up , period .
That 's just fucked up , man . That 's just ...
- I 'm sorry , man . - You chill . It 's all right .
- I 'm sorry , Heather . - It 's okay .
Who wants a cheeseburger ?
I do . I do .
- I got a cheeseburger in my back pocket . - Do you ?
Can I have a light to cut this ?
- You know what I fucking love ? - What ?
Mashed potatoes .
Me , too .
My mum 's mashed potatoes .
You 'll have them again very soon .
My mum 's mashed potatoes and a piece of ass .
Josh !
Fuck , Mike , we never go out of earshot .
- Josh ! - Hold on , calm down .
How could I ...
Josh !
He 's probably at the river or something .
If he was at the river , he could hear me from here .
- Josh ! - Josh !
Got to wait for him to respond .
Josh !
Do you remember what he said yesterday ?
What ?
About the shit on his bag , about how ...
Josh !
We didn 't even get woken up last night .
Noting even came to the tent last night .
Last night was a good night . There 's no way ...
He 's just ... he 's just ...
He went for a walk .
Josh , if you 're fucking with me I swear to God I 'm going to kill you !
Let 's go . We got to find him .
Come on .
We can 't even find the car !
How the fuck are we going to find Josh ?
Heather , come on .
- No . No . - Come on , come on .
- I 'm fine . - Come here , come on .
Relax , relax .
- He 's not ... - I 'm fine .
He 's just going ... He 's around .
- He 's just being a jerk . - Why isn 't he answering me ?
I don 't know . He just went out of earshot . That 's all .
All right , we 'll relax . We 'll break down the tent .
When he 's back , we 'll be ready to go , okay ?
I 'm losing my mind , Mike .
- Josh hasn 't come back . - Heather !
- I 'm over here , Mike . - Okay .
I don 't know if Josh ran off . I don 't ...
All his shit 's here .
I 've got the camera .
I don 't know how the fuck I 'm going to hike with that camera , but ...
You sure you want to take the fucking camera ?
We 've got to take the camera .
How do you feel about east ?
Well , south didn 't work .
Which wicked witch was worse ,
The Wicked Witch of the East or The Wicked Witch of the West ?
The Wicked Witch of the West was the bad one .
Well , let 's go east .
What the hell 's that ?
Josh ?
Josh !
We 're going to put up the tent now .
I 'm going to have a meatball .
- Just one meatball ? - And a long , red glass of wine .
Yeah , I would definitely have a whole fucking bottle of Bordeaux .
And a fresh pack of smokes .
Smokes would be good , and a long , hot bath .
And a big pumpkin pie .
A big pumpkin pie . With ice cream ?
- Warm , with melty ice cream . - Yeah , that sounds good .
What 's your favourite thing to do on a Sunday ?
It used to be drive to the woods and go hiking .
But I think that ...
- That might change now . - I think you can scratch that off .
Fuck ...
Should we go for him ?
Is it a trick ?
Josh ?
Josh !
- It 's stopped . - Josh !
Where 's it coming from ?
Josh !
Josh , where are you ? Tell me where you are !
Oh , my God !
No .
Fuck . Oh , God .
Do you think that it 's them fucking with us ?
I don 't know .
Josh !
- Is it over here ? - No , it 's over here .
We 'll look for him .
I don 't know if it 's really him . I don 't know if it 's really him .
Josh !
I don 't even know where to look .
Tell me where you are , Josh !
Mike ?
- Please don 't fall asleep . - I can 't fall asleep .
Whatever it is , knows that Josh is gone .
If that was Josh , he would have said where he was .
Whatever it was , sounded like Josh .
See .
I just want to show that Mike is here .
He 's sleeping .
Oh , shit .
What the hell is that ?
- Mike ? - What ?
There 's something out here .
What is it ?
Okay . Okay . Okay .
Okay , I 'm just going to move it from the front of the tent .
- Get rid of it . - Okay . I 'm taking it away .
I 'm taking it away from the front of the tent .
I 'm just throwing it .
Okay .
We 'll just keep walking .
- Okay ? - Okay .
- Just keep walking . - Okay .
I found some cigarettes .
I found them all the way at the bottom of my pack .
Which means we 're still alive , ' cause we 're smoking .
Okay .
I 'm just going to undo this very quietly and see what 's in here .
It 's all full of blood .
No .
Shit . Shit .
Shit .
Oh , my God .
Okay .
Okay , see ? Okay ...
Yeah ?
- What are you doing ? - I 'm okay . I 'm just washing my hands off .
- What ? - I 'm just washing my hands off .
I 'm fine . I 'm going to put my gloves on ...
I 'm going to put my gloves on my hands . I 'm going to put my gloves on my hands .
I 'm going to put my gloves on my hands .
- You all right ? - I 'm okay . I 'm okay .
Okay .
I 'm okay . I 'm okay .
- You need help ? - No , no . No , I don 't need any help .
I 'm okay .
- What happened ? - Nothing . Nothing happened .
I 'm just very hungry and I 'm very tired and I 'm very scared
- and I just want to go home , okay ? - Okay .
But I 'm fine , and we 're both okay .
Okay .
My hair 's caught .
Thank you . Thank you .
Okay . Okay . Okay . Okay .
2,130 games ,
one more season and Cal Ripken is king !
Cal Ripken is king !
And I won 't get to see it
' cause I 'll be in the woods !
Tell me you 're not eating a dry leaf .
I just want to apologise
to Mike 's mum
and Josh 's mum and my mum ...
And I 'm sorry to everyone .
I was very naive .
I was very naive . And very stupid .
But I shouldn 't have put other people in danger for something that was
all about me and my selfish motives .
I am so , so sorry
for everything that has happened
because in spite of what Mike says now , it is my fault
because it was my project
and I insisted .
I insisted on everything .
I insisted that we weren 't lost .
I insisted that we keep going .
I insisted that we walk south .
Everything had to be my way
and this is where we 've ended up .
And it 's all because of me that we 're here now ,
hungry and cold
and hunted .
I love you , Mum and Dad .
I am so sorry .
It was never my intention to hurt anyone and I just hope that 's clear .
I am so scared .
What is that ?
I 'm scared to close my eyes .
I 'm scared to open them .
Oh , God .
I 'm going to die out here .
Every night we just wait for them to come ...
Listen ...
- You got it ? - You ready ?
Somebody !
- Jesus Christ . - Please don 't go out there .
- Okay . - You ready ?
Here , take this light .
Please !
It 's okay . It can 't be him .
Please , follow my voice !
Holy shit . It 's a house .
- Holy shit . - Watch your step .
Holy shit . Holy shit .
Josh ?
Mike . Mike . Mike .
- Mike ? - Come on .
Mike , where the fuck are you ?
Come on . In the house .
Mike , do not go in there , please .
Mike .
Mike ?
Mike !
Mike , please .
- Mike , where are you ? - I 'm right here !
- Where is he ? - Mike , please don 't do this .
- Is he in here ? - No .
Heather !
Oh , Jesus .
Where is he ?
Do we go upstairs ?
I hear him . I hear him .
I hear you ! Josh ?
I 'm going upstairs !
Oh , God .
You hear that ?
Where is he ? Where are you ?
Come on . Josh ?
I hear him downstairs .
Come on ! I hear him downstairs !
- Mike ! - Come on !
- Mike ! - Josh !
Wait !
Oh , shit . Oh , shit .
- Josh ? - Mike !
- Josh , is that you down there ? - Mike !
Mike !
Josh .
Mike ! Mike !